Inventory of the Frederick Hutchinson Porter papers, 1880-1975
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
Frederick Hutchinson Porter papers
1880-1975
1920-1965
Porter, Frederick Hutchinson, 1890-1976.
00158
5 cubic feet (9 boxes)
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
Biography of Frederick Hutchinson Porter
Frederick Hutchinson "Bunk" Porter (1890-1976) was an architect in Cheyenne, Wyoming, where he was associated with the firm Baerrensen & Porter (1915-1921), F.H. Porter (1921-1944), Porter & Bradley (1944-1961), and Porter, Porter & Graves (1961-1965). He designed residential, commercial and public buildings throughout Wyoming. Among these were the federal building in Cheyenne and 40 buildings on the University of Wyoming campus in Laramie, Wyoming. He was also a water color painter whose works won numerous awards at Cheyenne fairs and exhibitions.
Scope and Content
The collection includes blueprints of numerous Wyoming buildings (1899-1965); architectural drawings; negatives; black and white photographs; 20 pieces of correspondence; biographical material; lists of buildings designed by Porter and his associates; scrapbooks related to his architectural projects; newspaper clippings; subject files; awards and certificates; and miscellaneous other materials.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions on the materials for research purposes, and the collection is open to the public.
Related Materials
There are no known other archival collections created by Frederick Hutchinson Porter at the date of processing.
Acquisition Information
Access Terms
University of Wyoming -- Buildings.; Baerrensen & Porter.; F.H. Porter (Firm); Porter & Bradley.; Porter, Porter & Graves.; Architecture -- Wyoming.; Architecture -- Wyoming -- Cheyenne.; Architecture -- Wyoming -- Laramie.; Architecture -- Designs and plans.; Architecture, Domestic -- Wyoming.; Architecture, Industrial -- Wyoming.; Public architecture -- Wyoming.; Public buildings -- Wyoming.; Public buildings -- United States.; Cheyenne (Wyo.) -- Buildings, structures, etc.; Laramie (Wyo.) -- Buildings, structures, etc.; Wyoming -- History -- 1890-1918.; Wyoming -- History -- 1919-1945.; Wyoming -- History -- 1946-; Blueprints.; Architectural drawings.; Photographs.; Negatives.; Scrapbooks.; Architects.
Architecture; Colleges and Universities; City Planning; Wyoming
Container List
- Pamphlet - "Architecture and Design" Vol. XIV by Frederic H. Porter and R. Watter Bradley, April 1950
- Architectural drawings:
  - The Bray House, undated (Box 7)
  - The Cutts House, undated (Box 7)
  - The Sparhawk House, undated (Box 7)
  - The Sowall House, undated (Box 7)
  - Congregational Church, Kittery, ME, undated (Box 7)
  - Details for houses in York, ME, undated (Box 7)
  - The Brooks House, undated (Box 7)
  - Doors from Machias and Machiasport, ME, undated (Box 7)
  - The Ruggles House, undated (Box 7)
- Addresses, essays, lectures, papers:
  - "From One of Buddha's Parables", undated (Box 2)
  - "Ramblings or Idle Thoughts of an Idle Fellow" - for Engineer's Club, April 8, 1933 (Box 2)
  - "Stylistic or Modernistic?", undated (Box 2)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 2)
- Articles and magazines:
  - "Architects Meet for Regional Conference" - Rocky Mountain Construction, October 15, 1958 (Box 2)
  - "Calendar of Western Events" - Architectural Record, October 1959 (Box 2)
  - "Pencil Point", undated (Box 2)
  - Pictures of University of Wyoming, undated (Box 2)
  - Porter, Frederic Hutchinson "Bunk" "Idle Thoughts on Architecture" Rocky Mountain Construction, December 23, 1964 (Box 2)
  - Porter, Frederic Hutchinson "A Survey of Existing Colonial Architecture in Maine" - Architectural Review, undated (Box 2)
  - "Thomas Hastings, 1860-1929" - Pencil Points, December 1929 (Box 2)
  - "Wyoming Architects Elect Officers at Regional Meeting" - Rocky Mountain Construction, November 1, 1958 (Box 2)
- Awards and certificates:
  - Awards
    - Superior - Western Plains Fair - Cheyenne, Wyoming, 1973 (Box 1)
    - First premium - Wyoming State Fair, 1954 (Box 1)
    - First premium - Wyoming State Fair - Cheyenne, Wyoming, 1969 (Box 1)
    - First place - Western Plains Fair - Cheyenne, Wyoming, 1973 (Box 1)
    - First premium - Western Plains Fair - Cheyenne, Wyoming, 1974 (Box 1)
    - First premium - Western Plains Fair - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 1)
    - Second place, undated (Box 1)
    - Second place - Western Plains Fair - Cheyenne Wyoming, 1974 (Box 1)
    - Second place - Cheyenne Artists Guild, undated (Box 1)
    - Second place - Western Plains Fair - Cheyenne Wyoming, undated (Box 1)
    - Third premium - Western Plains Fair - Cheyenne, Wyoming, 1973 (Box 1)
    - Third place, 1975 (Box 1)
    - Honorable mention - Cheyenne Artists Guild - semi-annual, May 1972 (Box 1)
    - Honorable mention - 17th Annual 5 State Show - North Platte Valley Artist Guild, undated (Box 1)
    - General award - Cheyenne Artists Guild - 3rd Regional Competition, undated (Box 1)
  - Certificates
    - The Grand Lodge of Ancient and Free and Accepted Masons of Wyoming - Frederick H. Porter - past Master Rocky Mountain Lodge no. 40, 1924 (Box 1)
    - Award to University of Wyoming from Institutions Magazine - first award, 1950 (Box 1)
    - The State of Texas - honorary citizen, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Member of the American Institute of Architects, April 13, 1925 (Box 1)
    - License to practice as architect in the State of Utah, November 17, 1952 (Box 1)
    - National Bureau for the Advancement of Music and Wyoming Choral and Instrumental Directors Association, May 7, 1938 (Box 1)
    - Certificate from American National Red Cross, December 1945 (Box 1)
    - Certificate from the American National Red Cross, January 1943 (Box 1)
    - Certificate from Nebraska State Board of Examiners for Professional Engineers and Architects, June 28, 1940 (Box 1)
    - Certificate to practice architecture in the State of Colorado, November 4, 1955 (Box 1)
    - Certificate to practice architecture in the State of Wyoming, May 18, 1951 (Box 1)
    - Certificate of appointment to the Wyoming State Board of Architects, March 1951 (Box 1)
    - Certificate to practice architecture in State of Colorado, March 3, 1942 (Box 1)
    - Honor award for superlative achievement in food service and sanitation, undated (Box 1)
- Biographical material:
  - Biography of Frederic Hutchinson Porter, undated (Box 2)
  - List of memberships of Frederic Hutchinson Porter and license numbers for Wyoming, Colorado, Nebraska, Utah, undated (Box 2)
  - Newspaper clippings regarding F.H. Porter, undated (Box 2)
  - Newspaper clipping - "Architect Porter Donates Collection to State Library", undated (Box 2)
  - Outline of biography of Frederic H. Porter, undated (Box 2)
- Blueprints:
  - Pine Cottage - State Training School - Lander, Wyoming, undated (Box 6)
  - Service station for the Frontier Refining Company, May 5, 1945 (Box 6)
  - Residences
    - A.V. McIvor - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - Edward C. Bon - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - Walter Bell - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - Thurman Arnold - Laramie, undated (Box 6)
    - House no. 14, Minnehaha Gardens, Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - W.H. Kleinke, Esq. - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - Fred Carlton - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - C. Howard Smith - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - R.S. Grier - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - Dr. F.A. Wilson - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - Dr. T.J. Henneberry - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - Ed. F. Murray - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - Dr. P.M. Cunningham - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - Mrs. John Connelly - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - F.C. Bliss - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - Paul H. Moore - Reality Co. - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - J.M. Garrett - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - Mr. C.G. Hancock - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - Max Davis - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - Mrs. Eva M. Guy - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
    - Mr. Herman Patternack - Cheyenne, undated (Box 6)
  - Memorial room and auditorium - Deming School - Cheyenne, Wyoming, August 20, 1946 (Box 6)
  - Grade school building - Ogallala, Nebraska, July 20, 1946 (Box 6)
  - Cheyenne Armory - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 6)
  - Art Abbey Residence - Cheyenne, Wyoming, May 1, 1965 (Box 6)
  - High school gymnasium - Cheyenne, Wyoming, May 10, 1948 (Box 6)
  - Parco Grade School, 1936 (Box 6)
  - Thomas Jefferson Grade School - Green River, 1940 (Box 6)
  - Additions to high school - Ogallala, Nebraska, March 10, 1948 (Box 6)
  - Post office and court house - upper floor plan, undated (Box 6)
  - Carbon County Court House - Rawlins, Wyoming, 1939 (Box 6)
  - Goshen County Jail - Torrington, Wyoming, 1929 (Box 6)
  - Mabel Fincher School - Cheyenne, Wyoming, 1940 (Box 6)
  - Riverton High School - Riverton, Wyoming, 1936 (Box 6)
  - Carbon County Courthouse - Rawlings, Wyoming, 1939 (Box 6)
  - House for Duncan Investment, Co., June 1, 1924 (Box 6)
  - New mantel in drawing room - Residence of Mrs. J.M. Carey - Cheyenne, Wyoming, June 5, 1924 (Box 6)
  - Unit storage shelving - Cheyenne Armory, August 27, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Carlson-Sloan, April 28, 1928 (Box 6)
  - Allison-Austin - Cheyenne, Wyoming, February 8, 1929 (Box 6)
  - Cottage for Fred Carlson - Cheyenne, Wyoming, August 13, 1925 (Box 6)
  - House for E.S. Sprague, Janaury 21, 1937 (Box 6)
  - Ingleside Grade School - Ingleside, Wyoming, undated (Box 6)
  - Sketches for high school building - Jackson, Wyoming, June 13, 1929 (Box 6)
  - Lander Grade School building - Lander, Wyoming, November 9, 1935 (Box 6)
  - Addition to residence for Mrs. Tracy S. McCraken, May 24, 1937 (Box 6)
  - Allison-Douglas House - Cheyenne, Wyoming, May 11, 1929 (Box 6)
  - Alterations to Scout Service Station - 16th and Warren, Cheyenne, Wyoming, January 28, 1939 (Box 6)
  - Community building - Worland, Wyoming, July 30, 1935 (Box 6)
  - School building - Shoshoni, Wyoming, May 30, 1935 (Box 6)
  - Floor plan - Alta Vista Grade School - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 6)
  - Golden Prairie School - Golden Prairie, Wyoming, 1936 (Box 6)
  - Residence for Miss Sarah D. Carey - Douglas, Wyoming, 1940 (Box 6)
  - Ahepa Lodge no. 211 - Cheyenne, Wyoming, May 29, 1945 (Box 6)
  - Alterations to opera house - block for J.M. Carey and Bros. - Wolders, February 1, 1939 (Box 6)
  - Alterations to roof - grade school - district 1 - Lusk, Wyoming, July 3, 1946 (Box 6)
  - Building for Rawlins Hotel Company - Rawlins, Wyoming, November 10, 1947 (Box 6)
  - Carbon County Court House - Rawlins, Wyoming, 1939 (Box 6)
  - Church building for Evangelical Lutheran Joint Synod - Orchard Valley, Cheyenne, Wyoming, March 10, 1945 (Box 6)
  - Deming School - additions - Cheyenne, Wyoming, March 20, 1952 (Box 6)
  - Kitchen remodeling - First Presbyterian Church - Cheyenne, Wyoming, August 14, 1964 (Box 6)
  - The Presidents Home - University of Wyoming, December 1, 1948 (Box 6)
  - Proposed Lodge I.O.O.F., March 9, 1962 (Box 6)
  - Rhone apartments, December 20, 1944 (Box 6)
  - School building for District 18 - Encampment, Wyoming, May 18, 1929 (Box 6)
  - Weston County Memorial Hospital, undated (Box 6)
  - Additions to school building for District 18 - Carbon County, Encampment, Wyoming, September 6, 1935 (Box 6)
  - Proposed Lodge I.O.O.F., March 14, 1962 (Box 6)
  - Cheyenne Armory - Cheyenne, Wyoming, Janaury 4, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Alterations to the bunkhouse - 1906 Bradley, Laramie, Wyoming, January 3, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Cheyenne Armory - Cheyenne, Wyoming, June 14, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Elementary school for School District One - Laramie County, Cheyenne, Wyoming, January 25, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Elementary school site - School District no. 1 - Cheyenne, Wyoming, December 18, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Shopping center - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 6)
  - Liquor Warehouse - State of Wyoming - Cheyenne, Wyoming, September 15, 1955 (Box 6)
  - Scottish Rite Temple - Cheyenne, Wyoming, August 15, 1946 (Box 6)
  - Wyoming State Office Building - Cheyenne, Wyoming, June 24, 1949 (Box 6)
  - Alterations to house at 3210 Dillon Avenue, November 8, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Carbon County Court House - Rawlins, Wyoming, September 10, 1938 (Box 6)
  - Elementary school site - School District no. 1 - Cheyenne, Wyoming, December 18, 1964 (Box 6)
  - L.M. Baggs Elementary School - School District no. 1 - Cheyenne, Wyoming, September 30, 1965 (Box 6)
  - New security cell block - Wyoming State Penitentiary - Rawlins, Wyoming, November 15, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Post office and court house - Cheyenne, Wyoming, 1961 (Box 6)
  - USP and FO Office 8 - Adjutant Generals Office Building - Cheyenne, Wyoming, November 15, 1967 (Box 6)
  - Elementary school for School District One - Laramie County, Cheyenne, Wyoming, Janaury 29, 1964 and February 3, 1965 (Box 6)
  - Post office and court house - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 6)
  - Addition to Johnson School Dist. #1 - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 6)
  - Cheyenne Armory - E.O.C. addition, November 1, 1964 (Box 6)
  - Addition to First Presbyterian Church - Cheyenne, Wyoming, September 1, 1960 (Box 6)
  - Kitchen remodel - First Presbyterian Church, undated (Box 6)
  - Studio building for Cheyenne Little Theater Players, Inc., October 25, 1957 (Box 6)
  - Alterations to house at 3210 Dillon Avenue for FHA, November 30, 1965 (Box 6)
  - School building - Bushnell, Nebraska, May 25, 1955 (Box 6)
  - Post office and court house, undated (Box 6)
  - Cheyenne Armory - Cheyenne, Wyoming by Larry R., March 3, 1964 (Box 6)
  - U.S. Public Building, 1899 (Box 6)
    - Details of approaches, etc. #1C, undated (Box 6)
    - Details of approaches, etc. J.K. Taylor, S. Architect #1C, undated (Box 6)
    - Map of lots 5,6,7, and 8, Block 329, Cheyenne, Wyoming, July 28, 1897 (Box 6)
    - First floor plan - #3A rev., undated (Box 6)
    - First floor plan - #3C, undated (Box 6)
    - Second floor plan - #4C, undated (Box 6)
    - Third floor plan - #5C, undated (Box 6)
    - Attic floor plan - #6C, undated (Box 6)
    - Basement plan - #7C, undated (Box 6)
    - Details of roof - #8C, undated (Box 6)
    - Ferguson St. elevation - Eddy St. elevation - #10C, undated (Box 6)
    - Rear elevation - #11C, undated (Box 6)
    - Transverse section - longitudinal section - #13C, undated (Box 6)
    - Details of main entrances - #15C, undated (Box 6)
    - Details of 1st and 2nd story stone-work - #16C, undated (Box 6)
    - Details of 2nd and 3rd St'y-Main-Cornice and C. - #17C, undated (Box 6)
    - Details of main cornice - gutter, etc. - #18C, undated (Box 6)
    - Court room details and other details in second story - #31C, undated (Box 6)
    - Court room finish - #34C, undated (Box 6)
  - Federal building US post office and court house, January 14, 1963 (Box 6)
  - Addition to Johnson School Dist. #1 - Cheyenne, Wyoming, September 11, 1944 (Box 6)
  - Doming Grade School and Alta Vista Grade School - Cheyenne, Wyoming, 1937-1950 (Box 6)
  - Fire station for City of Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 6)
  - Knights of Columbus Building and K.C. estimate, 1962-1963 (Box 6)
- Booklets, brochures, leaflets, pamphlets:
  - Federal building US post office and court house, June 1965 (Box 2)
  - First Presbyterian Church - "Seventy Five Years of History", 1869-1954 (Box 2)
  - Porter leaflets, vol. 1, no. 1 - Salem, Mass., 1896 (Box 2)
  - Prime commercial sites for sale in Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 2)
  - Salem Evening News, "Highlights in the History of Salem", undated (Box 2)
- Correspondence:
  - Dear little girl/Fred, August 1, 1912 (Box 2)
  - F.H. Porter, Jr./Willard Porter, January, 17, 1921 (Box 2)
  - Cheyenne Porters/Uncle Willard, December 31, 1931 (Box 2)
  - Mrs. F.H. Porter/Frederic, April 16, 1944 (Box 2)
  - Mr. Porter/Robert Russin, December 13, 1947 (Box 2)
  - Mrs. F.H. Porter/F.H. Porter (European trip), 1951 (Box 2)
  - Gentlemen/Bunk Porter, January 27, 1965 (Box 2)
  - Dear Bill/Bunk, May 13, 1965 (Box 2)
  - To whom it may concern/John Andrew Fisher and Rosemary M. Martin (list of books given to Wyoming State Library), December 30, 1965 (Box 2)
  - Mr. Porter/Lawson B. Knott, Jr., January 6, 1967 (Box 2)
  - Mr. Porter/Lawson B. Knott, Jr., October 25, 1968 (Box 2)
  - Frederic H. Porter/American Institute of Architects, December 5, 1968 (Box 2)
  - F.H. "Bunk" Porter/The Heels of Cheyenne Frontier Days, May 19, 1969 (Box 2)
  - Bunk/Wyoming State Board of Architects, January 8, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Mr. Porter/Mark Junge, December 20, 1971 (Box 2)
  - Mr. Porter/Mrs. Stan Hathaway, January 13, 1972 (Box 2)
  - Mr. Porter/Mark Junge, March 8, 1972 (Box 2)
  - Mr. Porter/Wm Seale, May 12, 1972 (Box 2)
  - Mr. Porter/E. Libby, May 8, 1975 (Box 2)
  - Mr. Porter/James T. Forrest, February 20, 1976 (Box 2)
  - Mr. Porter/J.T. Forrest, June 1, 1976 (Box 2)
- File folder - theatres, undated (Box 2)
- Illustrations, pencil drawings, prints (28 pieces), undated (Box 7)
- Lists:
  - Porter and Porter - architects - alphabetical index - all jobs, undated (Box 3)
  - Appraisal, January 24, 1966 (Box 3)
  - Porter, F.H. - architect - current commissions, 1940-1960 (Box 3)
  - Porter & Porter - architects - drawer index, undated (Box 3)
  - Job index, undated (Box 3)
  - List of architectural jobs, type of building, location, cost, date, completed, and resume, undated (Box 3)
  - List of buildings, undated (Box 3)
  - Porter and Porter - architects - numerical index - spiral notebook, undated (Box 3)
  - A partial list of commissions from work of Frederick Hutchinson Porter, 1920-1961 (Box 3)
  - School District no. 1, undated (Box 3)
  - Porter, F.H. - Wyoming Capitol Building, undated (Box 3)
  - Frederick H. Porter - University of Wyoming, undated (Box 3)
  - University of Wyoming Jobs by Porter, undated (Box 3)
- Negatives:
  - Unidentified negatives, undated (Box 3)
  - Salem folks, undated (Box 3)
  - The Bunkhouse and unidentified negatives, undated (Box 3)
  - Early architecture, undated (Box 3)
  - Maine, undated (Box 3)
  - House in Maine, undated (Box 3)
  - New Hampshire farm, undated (Box 3)
  - On Lake Erie, undated (Box 3)
  - Salem colonial, undated (Box 3)
  - Salt Lake and earlier, undated (Box 3)
  - Shaw's garden, undated (Box 3)
  - Sparta, Ill., undated (Box 3)
  - Unidentified buildings, undated (Box 3)
  - Unidentified buildings and doorways, undated (Box 3)
  - Unidentified buildings and people, undated (Box 3)
  - Unidentified house, undated (Box 3)
  - Old main, undated (Box 3)
  - Unidentified house (glass negative), undated (Box 3)
  - Child sitting under Christmas tree, undated (Box 3)
  - Unidentified houses, undated (Box 3)
- Newspaper clippings:
  - "The Daily Journal", February 10, 1959 (Box 4)
  - "The Wyoming Eagle", February 20, 1952 (Box 4)
  - "Wyoming State Tribune", February 19, 1952 and May 5, 1952 (Box 4)
  - Wyoming architecture, undated (Box 4)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr. and artistic work, undated (Box 4)
  - Porter family, undated (Box 4)
- Periodicals:
  - The Architectural Review, vols. VI-XII, 1918-1921 (Box 4)
  - University of Wyoming, Alumus, vol. XXIV, no.1, September-October 1976 (Box 4)
- Photographs:
  - Fred H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - All New England architecture, undated (Box 5)
  - Mrs. F.H. Porter, Sr. and son, undated (Box 5)
  - Unidentified man and woman (man in uniform), undated (Box 5)
  - Earl Benton, Dr. Pierce, Fred Porter, Sr. and Fred Porter III, undated (Box 5)
  - State courthouse and post office - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 5)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Fred H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Fred Porter (on left) and friend, color, undated (Box 5)
  - Fred Porter, Sr. and friends, undated (Box 5)
  - Unidentified boy and girl, undated (Box 5)
  - Sun dial, Miller's Falls, undated (Box 5)
  - 2 different poses of Grace Wastfield Porter, undated (Box 5)
  - First unit Memorial Hospital of Laramie County, Cheyenne, 1921 (Box 5)
  - Geo E. Brimmer House, polaroid, undated (Box 5)
  - The Bunkhouse, Porter Home, undated (Box 5)
  - Mrs. Fred H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Fred H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - Unidentified and two women, undated (Box 5)
  - Mill Stones, Turner's Falls, Mass., undated (Box 5)
  - Unidentified (probably F.H. Porter, Sr. as a young man), undated (Box 5)
  - Views of unidentified house, undated (Box 5)
  - Mr. and Mrs. F.H. Porter, Sr. and great granddaughter, undated (Box 5)
  - Unidentified lady, undated (Box 5)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Fred Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - Fred Porter, Jr., undated (Box 5)
  - Picture including Mr. and Mrs. F.H. Proter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - Unidentified man and woman, undated (Box 5)
  - Bunk Porter, friend and painting, undated (Box 5)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr. and painting, undated (Box 5)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Fred Porter, Sr., Mr. and Mrs. Fred Porter, Jr., undated (Box 5)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Fred Porter, Jr., undated (Box 5)
  - Mrs. F.H. Porter, Jr., undated (Box 5)
  - Photograph and painting, undated (Box 5)
  - Photograph of painting by F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - Ross Hall, undated (Box 5)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 5)
  - Cheyenne Frontier Days, undated (Box 5)
  - Mrs. F.H. Porter and first child (Willard), undated (Box 5)
  - Porter home - The Bunkhouse, undated (Box 5)
  - Parking lot behind Wyo Hall, University of Wyoming, undated (Box 5)
  - Fred Porter, Jr. (as a small child), undated (Box 5)
  - McCracken House - 2 story house with shutters - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 5)
  - Priscilla - Fred and mother at Whipple Hill - Danvers, MA - Porter's summer home, undated (Box 5)
  - Unidentified family, undated (Box 5)
  - The Bunkhouse - F.H. Porter, Sr. home, undated (Box 5)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr. residence, undated (Box 5)
  - Fred Porter, Jr. (as a child), undated (Box 5)
  - Fred Porter, Sr. and Jr. (as child), undated (Box 5)
  - Mrs. F.H. Porter, Sr. (bottom row, right side), undated (Box 5)
  - Mrs. F.H. Porter, Sr. and son, undated (Box 5)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Fred H. Porter, Sr. and son, undated (Box 5)
  - 3 generations of Porter family, undated (Box 5)
  - Grace Wastfield, undated (Box 5)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr. (as a young man), undated (Box 5)
  - Frederic Porter (3 years old), undated (Box 5)
  - Priscilla's mother at eighteen, undated (Box 5)
  - Grace Wastfield (Porter), undated (Box 5)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Fred Porter, Sr. (and children), undated (Box 5)
  - The Bunkhouse, undated (Box 5)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr. at 1 1/2 years old, undated (Box 5)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr. baby picture, undated (Box 5)
  - Unidentified, baby, young boy, and lady, undated (Box 5)
  - Unidentified young child, undated (Box 5)
  - Unidentified young woman, undated (Box 5)
  - Priscilla Lamson Porter and daughter Patricia, undated (Box 5)
  - Group photography (probably from European trip), undated (Box 5)
  - Interior of Bunkhouse - F.H. Porter, Sr. residence - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 5)
  - The Bunkhouse - F.H. Porter, Sr. home, undated (Box 5)
  - The Bunkhouse - residence of Frederic Hutchinson Porter - Cheyenne, Wyoming, undated (Box 5)
  - The Bunkhouse - Cheyenne, Wyoming - residence of F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - Emma Frances Porter, 1910 (Box 5)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - Mrs. F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - Fred H. Porter, Jr. (as a young man), undated (Box 5)
  - Group photograph - Mrs. F.H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - Group photograph - F.H. Porter, undated (Box 5)
  - Mrs. Porter and friend, undated (Box 5)
  - Bunk Porter's art display at art center, undated (Box 5)
  - Fred H. Porter, Sr., undated (Box 5)
  - F.H. Porter, Sr., January 1970 (Box 5)
  - Addie Burns Wastfield, undated (Box 5)
  - Frederic H. Porter, Jr. (as a child), undated (Box 5)
  - Unidentified man, undated (Box 5)
  - Frederic H. Porter, undated (Box 5)
  - Walter Dan Wastfield, undated (Box 5)